Daniel Aucar

Junior UI/UX Designer

Vancouver - BC danielaucarpro@gmail.com +55 19 981.442.686 danielaucar.com

I am a UI/UX Designer passionate about Design, with three years of experience in the graphic design industry, where I've done logos, and websites. Also, I have junior experience doing UI/UX Design at Vancouver Film School, and at FinalBoss, a brazilian company. I love to learn, and I can adapt to any team thanks to my patient and creative abilities.

EXPERIENCE

UI Artist

2019/10 - 2020/01 The Path of Calydra - FinalBoss, Unreal Grant Project, Brazil

(Unreal, third person, adventure, platform, PC and console, Team of 10)

Developed the art for the UI, with a modern vector style.

Pause Menu, Skill Selection Screen, Health Bar.

Did the iconography of all 16 skills the game have.

Junior UI/UX Design, Junior Level Designer

2018/10 - 2019/04 Old Man's Tale - Final Project at Vancouver Film School.

(Unity, On rail, first person shooter, PC, Team of 3)

Designed 5 minutes level inside Unity, using the Terrain Tool.

Developed the art direction for the UI/UX, with a illustrative stylized approach.

Main Menu, Pause Menu, Game Over Screen, Buttons, Sliders, HUD.

Coded the UI and the scree flow.

Screen Manager, Buttons, Sliders.

UI/UX Designer, and UI Programmer

72h Game Jam

Goblin EXE - Vancouver Film School Summer Game Jam 2018

(2D, side scroller, endless runner, Unity. Team of 5).

Developed the art direction for the UI, with a cyberpunk approach.

Buttons, HUD.

Coded the UI and screen flow.

Level Designer

2018/08 - 2018/10 Billy's Adventure - Vancouver Film School Portfolio Project 2018

(3D isometric arcade style game for the PC, Unity. Team of 3).

Designed a level from prototype to beta, using the pro builder tool.

Worked together with the artist in order to create landmarks and areas in each part of the level, such as playground, and barbecue. In order to reduced the possibility of the player to get lost.

Worked together with the programmer to decide which mechanics to implement, and how I should design the level to improve mechanics we already have.

OTHER EXPERIENCE

2017 - Present Aucarf Solid Waste Consulting - Brazil

EDUCATION

2010/01 - 2015/01 Faculdades de Campinas - Graphic Design Bachelor Degree

2018/04 - 2019/04 Vancouver Film School – Game Design Diploma

PASSIONS

Drawing and Art

Love to stay tuned about art, visit museums, and get references for my artwork.

Support e-sport

Huge fan of e-sports and the competitive online gaming scene in general.

SKILLS

UI/UX DESIGNER

Games Wireframing **Prototyping** Graphic Design

Adobe CC

Adobe Illustrator Adobe InDesign Adobe Photoshop

GAME DEVELOPER

Level Design

2D Layout Whiteboxing Set Dressing

3D Modelling

Autodesk Maya Zbrush

UV Mapping

Texturing

Substance Painter

CODE

C# Blue Print Visual Coding

Project Management Game Desing

SOFTWARE

Unity **Unreal Engine** Visual Studio Visual Code Microsoft Office

SOFT SKILLS

Organize Team working Receive Feedback Give Feedback Google Docs **Drawing**